Presenter: OK Team B. You have one minute to ask Team A questions.
George: Mmm let’s start with Nadine. Mike’s your hairdresser, right?
Nadine: Yes, we’re very good friends.
George: What’s the name of his salon?
Nadine: Er, it’s called er… Good Hair Day.
Charlie: Is Mike married?
Nadine: Er, yes he is.
Alice: Does he have children?
Nadine: Er, yes, er, no, he doesn’t. I don’t think he has children.
Alice: OK, so now Tyler. You say Mike’s your dentist. Where is his clinic?
Tyler: It’s er in central London, in Piccadilly.
Charlie: Are you and Mike friends?
Tyler: Well no, not really friends. It’s difficult to be friends with your dentist – it’s impossible to have a conversation!
George: Is he expensive?
Tyler: What do you think? He’s a dentist!
George: OK, James now. You say Mike’s a chef in a pub. What’s the name of the pub?
James: The Red Lion. It’s a great pub.
Charlie: What food does Mike cook?
James: Er, Great British food! Fish and chips, roast beef, things like that.
And he makes good sandwiches.
Alice: What’s his speciality?
James: Er, spaghetti carbonara.
Presenter: OK, team. Your time’s up.